{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047661386","data":{"timestamp":" 947047661385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047666484","data":{"timestamp":" 947047666484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047670289","data":{"timestamp":" 947047670289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047674130","data":{"timestamp":" 947047674130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047677611","data":{"timestamp":" 947047677611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047681418","data":{"timestamp":" 947047681418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047684814","data":{"timestamp":" 947047684814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047688789","data":{"timestamp":" 947047688789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047692273","data":{"timestamp":" 947047692273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047695873","data":{"timestamp":" 947047695873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047699484","data":{"timestamp":" 947047699484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047702899","data":{"timestamp":" 947047702899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047710762","data":{"timestamp":" 947047710762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047714875","data":{"timestamp":" 947047714874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047718519","data":{"timestamp":" 947047718518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047725830","data":{"timestamp":" 947047725830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047729381","data":{"timestamp":" 947047729381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047732678","data":{"timestamp":" 947047732678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047736431","data":{"timestamp":" 947047736431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047740152","data":{"timestamp":" 947047740152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047743822","data":{"timestamp":" 947047743822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047749288","data":{"timestamp":" 947047749288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047752866","data":{"timestamp":" 947047752866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047758016","data":{"timestamp":" 947047758016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047761814","data":{"timestamp":" 947047761814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047769001","data":{"timestamp":" 947047769001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047774770","data":{"timestamp":" 947047774769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6752c67c-27c4-4611-a97e-cd4320c93afb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047793920","data":{"timestamp":" 947047793920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047796037","data":{"timestamp":" 947047796036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047798161","data":{"timestamp":" 947047798160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047801406","data":{"timestamp":" 947047801405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047803675","data":{"timestamp":" 947047803674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047805937","data":{"timestamp":" 947047805936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047808780","data":{"timestamp":" 947047808779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047811014","data":{"timestamp":" 947047811013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047813231","data":{"timestamp":" 947047813230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047816453","data":{"timestamp":" 947047816452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047818541","data":{"timestamp":" 947047818541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047820611","data":{"timestamp":" 947047820610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047823594","data":{"timestamp":" 947047823593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047825831","data":{"timestamp":" 947047825831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047828075","data":{"timestamp":" 947047828074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047831145","data":{"timestamp":" 947047831144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047833521","data":{"timestamp":" 947047833520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047835899","data":{"timestamp":" 947047835898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047838993","data":{"timestamp":" 947047838992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047841098","data":{"timestamp":" 947047841097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047843228","data":{"timestamp":" 947047843227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047846406","data":{"timestamp":" 947047846406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047848608","data":{"timestamp":" 947047848606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047850780","data":{"timestamp":" 947047850779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047853979","data":{"timestamp":" 947047853978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047856397","data":{"timestamp":" 947047856396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047858804","data":{"timestamp":" 947047858803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047861984","data":{"timestamp":" 947047861983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047864258","data":{"timestamp":" 947047864258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047866510","data":{"timestamp":" 947047866509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047869480","data":{"timestamp":" 947047869479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047871698","data":{"timestamp":" 947047871697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047873914","data":{"timestamp":" 947047873914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047876951","data":{"timestamp":" 947047876951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047879319","data":{"timestamp":" 947047879318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047881704","data":{"timestamp":" 947047881703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047884831","data":{"timestamp":" 947047884830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047887196","data":{"timestamp":" 947047887195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047889604","data":{"timestamp":" 947047889603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047892617","data":{"timestamp":" 947047892616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047894901","data":{"timestamp":" 947047894900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047897173","data":{"timestamp":" 947047897172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047900420","data":{"timestamp":" 947047900420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047902727","data":{"timestamp":" 947047902727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047904965","data":{"timestamp":" 947047904965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047908352","data":{"timestamp":" 947047908352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047910818","data":{"timestamp":" 947047910817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047913268","data":{"timestamp":" 947047913267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047916192","data":{"timestamp":" 947047916191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047918409","data":{"timestamp":" 947047918408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047920632","data":{"timestamp":" 947047920631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047924050","data":{"timestamp":" 947047924049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047926405","data":{"timestamp":" 947047926404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047928740","data":{"timestamp":" 947047928739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047931876","data":{"timestamp":" 947047931876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047934138","data":{"timestamp":" 947047934137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047936445","data":{"timestamp":" 947047936444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047939403","data":{"timestamp":" 947047939403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047941486","data":{"timestamp":" 947047941486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047943592","data":{"timestamp":" 947047943591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047946758","data":{"timestamp":" 947047946757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047948988","data":{"timestamp":" 947047948987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047951239","data":{"timestamp":" 947047951238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047954479","data":{"timestamp":" 947047954479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047956690","data":{"timestamp":" 947047956689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047958933","data":{"timestamp":" 947047958932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047962215","data":{"timestamp":" 947047962214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047964535","data":{"timestamp":" 947047964535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047966807","data":{"timestamp":" 947047966807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047969815","data":{"timestamp":" 947047969815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047972092","data":{"timestamp":" 947047972092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047974427","data":{"timestamp":" 947047974427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047977798","data":{"timestamp":" 947047977797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047977933","data":{"timestamp":" 947047977933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 6fecb69a-e393-4705-9174-d8991a5f0618"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047996035","data":{"timestamp":" 947047996035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047996418","data":{"timestamp":" 947047996417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047996911","data":{"timestamp":" 947047996910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047997262","data":{"timestamp":" 947047997261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047997678","data":{"timestamp":" 947047997677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047998164","data":{"timestamp":" 947047998164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947047998398","data":{"timestamp":" 947047998398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048001605","data":{"timestamp":" 947048001604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048001640","data":{"timestamp":" 947048001640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048002364","data":{"timestamp":" 947048002363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048002769","data":{"timestamp":" 947048002769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048003078","data":{"timestamp":" 947048003077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048003293","data":{"timestamp":" 947048003293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048003499","data":{"timestamp":" 947048003498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048003827","data":{"timestamp":" 947048003826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048004063","data":{"timestamp":" 947048004063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048007261","data":{"timestamp":" 947048007260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048007673","data":{"timestamp":" 947048007673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048010240","data":{"timestamp":" 947048010239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048010452","data":{"timestamp":" 947048010452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048010664","data":{"timestamp":" 947048010664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048014194","data":{"timestamp":" 947048014193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048018016","data":{"timestamp":" 947048018015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048019052","data":{"timestamp":" 947048019051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048021801","data":{"timestamp":" 947048021800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048022186","data":{"timestamp":" 947048022185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048022680","data":{"timestamp":" 947048022680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048023034","data":{"timestamp":" 947048023034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048023451","data":{"timestamp":" 947048023450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048023937","data":{"timestamp":" 947048023936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048024172","data":{"timestamp":" 947048024171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048027397","data":{"timestamp":" 947048027396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048027430","data":{"timestamp":" 947048027430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048028159","data":{"timestamp":" 947048028158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048028561","data":{"timestamp":" 947048028560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048028868","data":{"timestamp":" 947048028868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048029073","data":{"timestamp":" 947048029073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048029279","data":{"timestamp":" 947048029279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048029605","data":{"timestamp":" 947048029605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048029843","data":{"timestamp":" 947048029842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048032482","data":{"timestamp":" 947048032481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048032600","data":{"timestamp":" 947048032600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 64ebed87-8140-4a92-a5dc-e894f040133c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048045541","data":{"timestamp":" 947048045541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048045924","data":{"timestamp":" 947048045924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048046420","data":{"timestamp":" 947048046419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048046774","data":{"timestamp":" 947048046774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048047191","data":{"timestamp":" 947048047191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048047681","data":{"timestamp":" 947048047680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048047918","data":{"timestamp":" 947048047917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048051102","data":{"timestamp":" 947048051101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048051135","data":{"timestamp":" 947048051135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048051862","data":{"timestamp":" 947048051862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048052270","data":{"timestamp":" 947048052270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048052576","data":{"timestamp":" 947048052576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048052795","data":{"timestamp":" 947048052794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048053001","data":{"timestamp":" 947048053000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048053332","data":{"timestamp":" 947048053331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048053568","data":{"timestamp":" 947048053567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048056755","data":{"timestamp":" 947048056754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048057173","data":{"timestamp":" 947048057172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048059711","data":{"timestamp":" 947048059710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048059925","data":{"timestamp":" 947048059924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048060140","data":{"timestamp":" 947048060138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048063692","data":{"timestamp":" 947048063690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048067518","data":{"timestamp":" 947048067517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048068554","data":{"timestamp":" 947048068553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048071290","data":{"timestamp":" 947048071289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048071675","data":{"timestamp":" 947048071674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048072169","data":{"timestamp":" 947048072168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048072523","data":{"timestamp":" 947048072522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048072938","data":{"timestamp":" 947048072937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048073425","data":{"timestamp":" 947048073425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048073660","data":{"timestamp":" 947048073659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048076892","data":{"timestamp":" 947048076891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048076932","data":{"timestamp":" 947048076932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048077661","data":{"timestamp":" 947048077660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048078064","data":{"timestamp":" 947048078064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048078373","data":{"timestamp":" 947048078372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048078589","data":{"timestamp":" 947048078589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048078797","data":{"timestamp":" 947048078797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048079131","data":{"timestamp":" 947048079130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048079369","data":{"timestamp":" 947048079368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048081999","data":{"timestamp":" 947048081997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048082127","data":{"timestamp":" 947048082127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" bea7aaf3-04c6-4c64-aab2-241fe78449ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048109703","data":{"timestamp":" 947048109702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048114959","data":{"timestamp":" 947048114959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048116602","data":{"timestamp":" 947048116601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048119203","data":{"timestamp":" 947048119202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" START_WANAWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048123315","data":{"timestamp":" 947048123314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" START_WANAWAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048124874","data":{"timestamp":" 947048124873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048126476","data":{"timestamp":" 947048126475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048129195","data":{"timestamp":" 947048129195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048130847","data":{"timestamp":" 947048130846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATOTO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048133542","data":{"timestamp":" 947048133542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATOTO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048135184","data":{"timestamp":" 947048135183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048137942","data":{"timestamp":" 947048137941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" START_WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048141659","data":{"timestamp":" 947048141659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048143255","data":{"timestamp":" 947048143254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKIRUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048153340","data":{"timestamp":" 947048153340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKIRUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048154964","data":{"timestamp":" 947048154964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WADUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048157868","data":{"timestamp":" 947048157868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WADUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048159461","data":{"timestamp":" 947048159460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048162112","data":{"timestamp":" 947048162112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048163722","data":{"timestamp":" 947048163721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048168394","data":{"timestamp":" 947048168393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" START_WALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048173350","data":{"timestamp":" 947048173350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048174988","data":{"timestamp":" 947048174987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048177447","data":{"timestamp":" 947048177446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048179473","data":{"timestamp":" 947048179471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048179607","data":{"timestamp":" 947048179607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 3dea36bf-73db-4226-9fc4-5f47c24f5d64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048193586","data":{"timestamp":" 947048193585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048196676","data":{"timestamp":" 947048196676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" START_WAKULIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048197684","data":{"timestamp":" 947048197684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048199308","data":{"timestamp":" 947048199307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048214276","data":{"timestamp":" 947048214276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048215894","data":{"timestamp":" 947048215894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048222822","data":{"timestamp":" 947048222821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048224498","data":{"timestamp":" 947048224498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048224520","data":{"timestamp":" 947048224519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048242885","data":{"timestamp":" 947048242885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048243009","data":{"timestamp":" 947048243009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 9dee4a8d-fc1f-4256-9064-b94e9293607c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048256834","data":{"timestamp":" 947048256833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048262556","data":{"timestamp":" 947048262555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048264158","data":{"timestamp":" 947048264157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048266784","data":{"timestamp":" 947048266782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WANAWAKE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048268390","data":{"timestamp":" 947048268389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048272086","data":{"timestamp":" 947048272086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAVU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048273694","data":{"timestamp":" 947048273693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATOTO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048276665","data":{"timestamp":" 947048276664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATOTO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048278293","data":{"timestamp":" 947048278292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048283994","data":{"timestamp":" 947048283993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKITEMBEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048285614","data":{"timestamp":" 947048285613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKIRUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048291419","data":{"timestamp":" 947048291419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WAKIRUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048293056","data":{"timestamp":" 947048293056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WADUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048295694","data":{"timestamp":" 947048295693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WADUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048297296","data":{"timestamp":" 947048297295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048300363","data":{"timestamp":" 947048300362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048301981","data":{"timestamp":" 947048301980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048304423","data":{"timestamp":" 947048304423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048306028","data":{"timestamp":" 947048306027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048311145","data":{"timestamp":" 947048311145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048313162","data":{"timestamp":" 947048313161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947048313273","data":{"timestamp":" 947048313273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_074727"," gameId":" 5a7f0bc7-e379-438e-b6aa-ee7069d58448"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" WATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}